{"creationDate":"2018-04-28 11:57:51","type":"questionnaire","id":"xmfifia388jgc7thdt","title":"Bricomarché departementos numéros 2017","questions":[{"id":"9bwo3n36zy7jgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Jardim (quota %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"yw0k4f7lhrjgc7thdt","answer":"19.84","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"uyt2bstcmhejgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Construçao (quota %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"y32ygaezlafjgc7thdt","answer":"4.58","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"m6acdvw2k58jgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Bricolage (quota %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"nisxspafmjgc7thdt","answer":"44.83","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"kg5i5tc3gsjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Decoracao (quota %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"xj0841usx9mjgc7thdt","answer":"25.64","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"h9q4bf4w92djgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Serviço (quota %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"f3ojw5sxi8jgc7thdt","answer":"0.18","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"x2t4fanhoajgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Petshop (quota %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"zv8xyayn4aajgc7thdt","answer":"4.92","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"g9xjsj832ypjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Jardim (margen %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"g0tpyhgybqojgc7thdt","answer":"25.37","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"ellerlsdc9gjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Construçao (margen %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"tzy0eggz7bjgc7thdt","answer":"21.12","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"i4pkwvj2hojgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Bricolage (margen %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"ecom3o0wfrsjgc7thdt","answer":"25.43","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"ao4r60cejqmjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Decoraçao (margen %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"bu45hx2hlvbjgc7thdt","answer":"28.33","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"jqfryofld9ajgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Serviços (margen %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"fza8ukwp90cjgc7thdt","answer":"75.63","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"hc152juksvljgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Petshop (margen %)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"6d92a44yslajgc7thdt","answer":"20.26","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false},{"id":"6a2zz3kzmybjgc7thdt","questionLabel":"Numéros 2017","answerLabelOk":"","answerLabelNok":"","question":"Total margem (%)","detail":"","answers":[{"id":"1qm6jiy2tmvjgc7thdt","answer":"25.80","correctDistance":0,"point":1}],"point":1,"showAnwsers":false}],"fileName":"xmfifia388jgc7thdt.json","modificationDate":"2018-04-28 14:27:34","disabled":true}